She's regretting saying yes to this.
Oh God, the bags over the camera, this is hilarious.
Billie Eilish, we meet again.
We meet again.
Welcome to my rage room.
What the hell is going on?
You must hit whatever you want to hit.
We've got questions from our listeners.
I want to talk about the unbelievable 3D movie.
Should I just start?
Yes, should I just start?
I think so.
Start, let's go.
Go!
That was glass.
Yeah, it was.
Yeah!
Hit it!
Oh!
Feel good?
Yes, it feels so good.
It does feel good.
Woo!
Part of the serenity of Rage Room is the being alone, but with the audience
is insane.
My heart's beating though, right?
Yeah, me too.
Doesn't it feel good?
Feels good.
Alive.
Okay, here's a question in the rubble.
Okay.
Simon says...
Oh, God.
If you could go back and re-record a song, which song would you pick and
why?
Simon says...
Well, no, it's not.
He is a man called Simon.
Oh.
And he's just saying.
Simon says...
Oh, so we're not playing the game of Simon Chips.
Simon says put your hands on your head.
Put your hands on your hips.
You immediately...
Simon says put your hands on your hips.
Go.
Simon says spin round.
Simon says answer this question from Simon.
Okay.
If you could go back and re-record a song, Which song would you pick and
why?
Mmm.
Probably something from when I was like 15.
Because.
Okay.
Because I just sound like a little baby.
I would probably just rerecord one of those.
Like maybe...
Mmm...
Maybe I don't want to be you anymore or something.
But you're not re-recording Ocean Eyes though, are you?
No.
Because that's just...
That's too pure.
That's a moment.
That's a little baby girl.
Before I smash something to smithereens...
Yes?
Can I just say, I love the movie so much.
Thank you, Greg!
Having seen the show at the O2...
Oh my god, yes!
Then to see it in 3D...
It's pretty cool, right?
But James Cameron, just doing his thing, him just going, do we make it like
Titanic or do we make it like Avatar?
No, no, no, no, no.
Do you want to be painted blue?
Where do we put the boat?
No, but it's unbelievable.
You just look like you're having the time of your life doing it.
Grabbing the camera, running under the stage.
It's so much joy.
It's really, really fun.
Yes, it's a lot of joy.
And I think this was like my favorite tour.
So I think like I'm really excited that that's the tour that we have on
camera.
In 3D.
Shouldn't we do a throw it up and hit it with like with the pole
like it's a baseball?
Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm going to miss.
Ready?
It's going to be good.
All right, go.
You can barely see.
Yeah.
Great.
First.
First goal.
And that was 11-year-old Rose's question.
Oh.
Shattered on the floor.
What's your favorite album to perform?
Hit Me Hard and Soft.
Of course.
Yeah, those are some good songs.
I like that album a lot.
And it's all new.
Everything that's new is fun.
Anyway, dogs.
Yeah?
You invite dogs to the show.
Now you just turned it into a bar brawl.
Well, so...
One of my favorite bits of this whole thing is you just sitting on the
floor smashing bottles on a pipe.
Do it!
It feels really good.
Here.
Sorry, wait, I didn't even answer you.
Oh, what was I talking about?
Okay, dogs.
Well, so I started in like 2018 or 2019 at shows having
whatever, having any rescue organization in whatever city we're playing bring like dogs and
puppies who are like up for adoption and need homes or fosters or whatever it
is.
The amount of dogs and puppies that have been adopted on my tour by my
team, by me, by my band, It's really pretty amazing.
Um, Billy, what I should...
Excuse me.
I'm trying to make a very serious point.
Yeah?
What I should say, um, should have said this earlier.
Wait.
Every...
You want to bat this one?
I'd love to.
Which way do you want to go?
I'll go that way, so it's away from you.
Okay.
Here she goes.
Yay!
What I was about to say.
Yes?
Everything in here was not fit for purpose and is going to be recycled.
Right.
Okay.
Well, I know that you're a sustainable queen as well.
No, it's true.
That's what I like to hear.
I was hoping.
Yeah.
Recycled.
Like it's like...
Yeah, this is going to a local primary school.
Yeah, so they're gonna print off all their little pictures on it that's good Sam
and Alex
They say was an amazing book yeah, it wasn't that good sorry gone are you
thinking of anyone as you hit that
No, just thinking of hitting it.
What about you?
There's somebody you're thinking of yeah Yeah, there is someone, but I can't say.
Yes, you can.
Bleep it out.
Who is it?
It's currently...
Yeah?
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
Okay, it's...
Okay, I'll tell you who else I'm thinking about.
Any...
Is it...
Always.
Yeah.
Yeah!
This one's for anyone who's mean to dogs.
That's right.
Ah!
We need a smashing song.
What smashing song do you want?
Play ya, play ya.
Play something beautiful.
There we go, that's a great idea.
Should play Caribbean Blue by Enya.
Oh, get Enya on.
Thank you.
Love you, dog.